Edward C. Blomeyer photographic collection, Inclusive: 1906-1923, Bulk: 1912-1920
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- Texas., 1906-1920; 2
  - Waco, 1912-1920; 1
    - General, 1912-1920; 4
      - Waco: General: Auto Race 724-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-724.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:92)
      - Waco: General: Horse Race, Gurley Park, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1:93)
      - Waco: General: Horse Race, Gurley Park 775-4: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-775.4.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 1:94)
      - Waco: General: Bird’s Eye View 496-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-496.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:95)
      - Waco: General: Bird’s Eye View 803-1: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-803.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:96)
      - Waco: General: Bird’s Eye View 803-2: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-803.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:97)
      - Waco: General: Church Unidentified-Waco?, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:98)
      - Waco: General: Monument Indian Spring Park, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:99)
      - Waco: General: July 4th Parade: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-695.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:100)
      - Waco: General: July 4th Parade: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-776.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:101)
      - Waco: General: Camp MacArthur: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-760.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:102)
      - Waco: General: Rich Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-909.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:103)
      - Waco: General: Rich Field, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:104)
      - Waco: General: Rich Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-759.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:105)
      - Waco: General: Rich Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-719.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:106)
      - Waco: General: Rich Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-719.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:107)
      - Waco: General: Rich Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-909.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:108)
      - Waco: General: Rich Field: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-720.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:109)
      - Waco: General: Rich Field, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:110)
      - Waco: General: Downtown, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:111)
      - Waco: General: Downtown: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-696.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:112)
      - Waco: General: Downtown: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-786.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:113)
      - Waco: General: Downtown: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-786.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:114)
      - Waco: General: Shakespeare Monument: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-705.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:115)
      - Waco: General: Graham Road, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:116)
      - Waco: General: Street Scenes: Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-906.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:117)
      - Waco: General: Street Scenes: Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-695.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:118)
      - Waco: General: Street Scenes: Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-695.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:119)
      - Waco: General: Street Scenes: Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-705.3.tif, 1917 May 1 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:120)
      - Waco: General: Street Scenes: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-816.4.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:121)
      - Waco: General: Street Scenes, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:122)
      - Waco: General: Street Scenes, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:123)
      - Waco: General: Homes Construction: “Adding a new story under a house”, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:124)
      - Waco: General: Homes: Construction: “Adding a new story under a house”, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:125)
      - Waco: General: Homes: Blomeyer House-Garden, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:126)
      - Waco: General: Homes: John Baker Home-Baker Lane Entrance, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:127)
      - Waco: General: Natural Spring with Amma Blomeyer and sons, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:128)
      - Waco: General: D.A.R. Indian Springs Park Monument, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:129)
      - Waco: General: Unidentified Church-Waco? Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-761.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:130)
      - Waco: General: War Service Board-Waco? Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-761.2.tif, 1918 May 2 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:131)
      - Waco: General: War Service Board-Waco? Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-txwaco-761.3.tif, 1918 May 2 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:132)
      - Waco: General: Mailboxes, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:133)
      - Waco: General: Mailboxes, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:134)
      - Waco: General: Huaco Clubhouse Fire Aftermath, 1917 January 4 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:135)
      - Waco: General: Huaco Clubhouse Fire Aftermath, 1917 January 4 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:136)
      - Waco: General: Huaco Clubhouse Fire Aftermath, 1917 January 4 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:137)
      - Waco: General: Huaco Clubhouse Fire Aftermath, 1917 January 4 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:138)
      - Waco: General: Huaco Clubhouse Fire Aftermath, 1917 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Waco: General, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - Waco: General, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Central and South Texas, 2
    This subseries shows images of Texas such as Austin, Galveston, Port Aransas, San Antonio, Waxahachie, Tyler, and New Braunfels. Other scenes show rural gravel roads in or around McLennan County and the rough conditions early motorists faced. Other pictures show examples of the many rail roads and an unidentified oil and natural gas "boomtown."
    - Railroad, 1912-1920; 1
      This series of photographs consists mainly of steam locomotives hauling passengers and freight by the Katy (Missouri, Kansas, and Texas-M.K.& T.) Railroad of Texas. Some images may have been taken in Waco near the Katy depot but most are taken in rural areas in or around McLennan County, Texas.
      A passenger and freight steam locomotive believed to be from the from the Katy (Missouri Kansas and Texas-M.K.&T.) Railroad is shown passing through an unknown rural location. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-879.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      Shown in this image is a passenger train powered by 2 steam locomotive of the Katy (Missouri Kansas and Texas-M.K.&T.) Railroad. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-436.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      Shown in this image is a passenger train powered by two steam locomotives of the Katy (Missouri Kansas and Texas-M.K.&T.) Railroad. Waco's well-known photographer, Fred Gildersleeve, is shown posing next to the tree on the right of the picture. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-508.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      A steam locomotive of the Katy (Missouri Kansas and Texas-M.K.&T.) Railroad is shown at a crossing. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-438.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      A close-up view of a steam locomotive hauling freight is shown in this photo. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-433.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      A passenger steam train from the Katy (Missouri Kansas and Texas-M.K.&T.) Railroad is shown passing through an unknown rural location. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-440.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, February 24, 1918.
      A passenger and freight steam locomotive of the Katy (Missouri Kansas and Texas-M.K.&T.) Railroad passes in or near Waco, Texas. An advertisement for Waco's famous department store, Sanger Brother's, is seen along the line to the left. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-693.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
      A steam locomotive with passenger and freights cars passes through one of the many rail lines through McLennan County, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-436.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, May 28, 1917.
      A passenger steam train with passengers hanging out of the windows is shown passing through an unknown rural location. This could possibly be a troop train going to or from Camp MacArthur. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-501.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      This image shows a steam passenger locomotive in an unknown location. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ½ by 3 ½ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-688.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-693.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:139)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-816.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:140)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-784.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:141)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-783.4.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:142)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-905.22.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:143)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Flood, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:144)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Flood, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:145)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Flood: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-784.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:146)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Flood: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-910.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:147)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad, 1912-1920 (Folder 2:148)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-778.4.tif, 1912-1920 (Folder 2:149)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-687.4.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:150)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-514.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:151)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex 687.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:152)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-688.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:153)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-687.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:154)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad with Sanger Bros. Sign: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-437.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:155)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-508.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:156)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Interurban on Bridge: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-789.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:157)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-879.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:158)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-501.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:159)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-433.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:160)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-438.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:161)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:162)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-436.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:163)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-440.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:164)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:165)
      - Central and South Texas: Railroad, 1912-1920 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920; 2
      E.C. Blomeyer captured several scenes of the roads around Waco, McLennan County, and the central Texas area at a time when they were suited more for wagons than automobiles. He consistently photographed his Ford Model-T along these roads as if to record the adverse conditions he encountered in his travels.
      This scenic view is believed to be in the Texas hill country. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-766.2. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      A rural road scene taken in the central Texas area. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-515.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      This road is in or on the outskirts of the city of Waco. An advertisement for Waco's McLendon Hardware store is seen to the right. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-693.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      E.C. Blomeyer's caption on the back of the printed version of this photograph reads: "A Texas road." The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-802.1.tif. Photo taken circa 1917.
      This road is in or on the outskirts of the city of Waco. On the license plate of the Ford Model-T, pictured, is its number, then "WACO." The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-721.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      E.C. Blomeyer's caption on the back of the printed version of this photograph reads: "Panorama-on the road to McGregor [Texas]." The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-789.1.tif. Photo taken circa 1917.
      A stop along the road, possibly around the Waco area; the two men are employees of The Texas Telephone Company. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-901.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      Fixing a flat tire on a rural Texas road. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4 inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-783.2.tif. Photo taken circa 1917.
      This road is believed to be in or around the Waco city limits. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-802.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      A farm scene taken from along the side of a rural Texas road. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-515.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      Two girls pick flowers along a rural road side somewhere in central Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-766.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1917.
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-515.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:166)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-802.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:167)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:168)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:169)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:170)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-783.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:171)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:172)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:173)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-721.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:174)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-906.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:175)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-766.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:176)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-802.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:177)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:178)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:179)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:180)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:181)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:182)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-516.3.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:183)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:184)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-515.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:185)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:186)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:187)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: McGregor: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-789.1.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:188)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos:, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:189)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Moody: Whitzson RD, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:190)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Hill Country/Bosque River: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-766.2.tif, 1917 June 18 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:191)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Waco Outskirts: Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer 3886-centexsotex-693.2.tif, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:192)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Pole with Ingrown Barbed Wire, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:193)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:194)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Car Facing Winding Gravel Road, 1912-1920 (Box 2 OVZ, Folder 2:195)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Bridge, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:196)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos: Bridge, 1912-1920 (Box 1 OVZ, Folder 2:197)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Rural Roadways and Autos, 1912-1920 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Cities, Sites, and Coastal Scenes, 1906-1920; 3
      This group of images includes some of Texas' most prominent sites such as the State Capitol in Austin, the Alamo in San Antonio, and the Texas gulf coast. Coastal images include the Galveston Causeway, Hotel Galvez, and Galveston Seawall.
      San Antonio: This photograph was taken on the Alamo Plaza, San Antonio, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-759.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
      Gulf Coast: This photograph was taken in an unknown location on the Gulf Coast of Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-759.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
      San Antonio: This image shows the exterior of the Alamo, San Antonio, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-396.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
      Austin: A bird's eye view of downtown Austin, Texas, showing some of its churches in the distance. The digital image is from a scan of a 1 ¾ by 2 ¾-inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-800.10.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
      San Antonio: This image shows the exterior of the Alamo, San Antonio, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-395.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
      San Antonio: The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-397.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1918.
      Austin: The Texas State Capitol is photographed from Congress Avenue, Austin, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-688.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1916.
      Austin: This photograph was taken from the front steps of the Texas State Capitol building in Austin. The digital image is from a scan of a 1 ¾ by 2 ¾-inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-800.08.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
      Gulf Coast: An unknown man stands outside of the Hotel Galvez, Galveston Island, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 1 ¾ by 2 ¾-inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-816.11.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
      San Antonio: This photograph was taken on the Alamo Plaza, San Antonio, Texas. It shows the Alamo in the distance and just to the right, the Menger Hotel is situated behind the trees and surrounded by vehicles of all types. E.C. Blomeyer took this photograph in about 1906, prior to moving to this state in 1912. The digital image is from a scan of a 3 ¼ by 4 ½-inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-781.tif.
      Gulf Coast: The seawall is seen in front of the Hotel Galvez, Galveston Island, Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 1 ¾ by 2 ¾-inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-922.4.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
      Gulf Coast: This photograph was taken in an unknown location on the Gulf Coast of Texas. The digital image is from a scan of a 6 by 3 ¾ inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-785.2.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.
      Austin: This photograph shows a bird's eye view of Congress Avenue and the Texas State Capitol in Austin. The digital image is from a scan of a 1 ¾ by 2 ¾-inch, cellulose nitrate negative. Digital ID: tx-phoarch-blomeyer_3886-centexsotex-794.1.tif. Photo taken by E.C. Blomeyer, circa 1912.